<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cat\'s BMI - Feline BMI Calculator</string>
    <string name="GoBtn">Start</string>
    <string name="main_measure_body_comment">Please measure the dimensions</string>
    <string name="body_measure">Body circumference</string>
    <string name="leg_measure">Leg length</string>
    <string name="centimeter">Cm</string>
    <string name="calculation">Calculate</string>
    <string name="formulaText">Formula</string>
    <string name="formula">Feline Body Mass Index (FBMI)(%) = ((((Body circumference) / 0.7062) - Leg length) / 0.9156) - Leg length)</string>
    <string name="closeBtn">Close</string>
    <string name="bodyMeasureTooltipText">Measure the circumference of your cat\'s rib cage. (The level of the 9th rib is ideal)</string>
    <string name="legMeasureTooltipText">Measure the length of the lower back leg from the knee to the ankle.</string>
    <string name="readmeText">All information that appears later should be used for reference only, and be sure to consult a doctor or specialist for a final medical decision.</string>
    <string name="readmeYes">Yes</string>
    <string name="readmeNo">No</string>
    <string name="splash_title">Cat\'s BMI - Feline BMI Calculator</string>
    <string name="yourCatIs">Your cat\'s</string>
    <string name="FBMI">BMI(%) is :</string>
    <string name="FBMIPercent">%</string>
    <string name="Is">.</string>
    <string name="SeverelyUnderweight">Severely Under Weight</string>
    <string name="Underweight">Under Weight</string>
    <string name="TooThin">Too Thin</string>
    <string name="Ideal">Ideal</string>
    <string name="AboveIdeal">Above Ideal</string>
    <string name="Overweight">Over Weight</string>
    <string name="Obese">Obese</string>
    <string name="SeverelyObese">Severely Obese</string>
    <string name="status">Status</string>
    <string name="Diagnosis">Diagnosis</string>
    <string name="tv1_status_text">Your cat is seriously underweight. No fat is visible or palpable.The belly is thin and the bones of the whole body, including ribs and back bones, are easily observed with the eyes. It feels like only leather is left.</string>
    <string name="tv2_status_text">Your cat is underweight. You can\'t see or touch fat well. Stomach is slim and ribs are easily touched. When you viewed with the eyes, the back and ribs are easily observed. When viewed from above, it feels very skinny.</string>
    <string name="tv3_status_text">Your cat is skinny. You can see very little fat. Stomach is slim and ribs easily palpable with minimal fat covering. Lumbar vertebrae obvious. Obvious waist behind ribs. minimal abdominal fat.</string>
    <string name="tv4_status_text">Your cat is ideal weight that\'s well-balanced. The belly is flat and has a little fat. If you touch it with your hands, you can feel the ribs. When viewed from above, the location of the waist is confirmed.</string>
    <string name="tv5_status_text">Your cat is ideal weight that\'s well-balanced. The belly is flat and has a little fat. If you touch it with your hands, you can feel the ribs. When viewed from above, the location of the waist is confirmed.</string>
    <string name="tv6_status_text">Your cat is a weight that feels a little chubby. The ribs are palpable with a little excess fat. The belly has a lot of fat, so it goes down to some extent. There is no curvature of the waist when viewed from above.</string>
    <string name="tv7_status_text">Your cat is overweight. The fat is so thick it\'s hard to touch the ribs. The belly has a lot of fat, so it goes down a lot. When viewed from above, the waist is rounded.</string>
    <string name="tv8_status_text">Your cat is obesity. There is so much fat that the ribs are no longer palpable. There is too much fat in the stomach, so it descends badly and wobbles when walking. When viewed from above, the waist is very rounded.</string>
    <string name="tv9_status_text">Your cat is serious obesity. The fat builds up so badly that the ribs are not palpable at all. There is too much fat in the stomach, so it descends badly and sometimes touches the floor when walking. The waist is hard and round with a lot of fat accumulated. She\'s face also gain weight.</string>
    <string name="tv1_diag_text">Many people worry about their cats gaining weight, but unintentional weight loss can also be a serious problem. Depending on the cause of your cat\'s weight loss, she may have a decreased appetite or may not eat at all. Cats with anorexia that refuse to eat can develop hepatic lipidosis or fatty liver, which is very dangerous for their health. However, even if a cat eats a normal amount of food, it may lose weight. One of the causes of weight loss in cats due to disease is diabetes. Cats with diabetes have a loss of appetite and drink too much water, so they urinate more than usual. Or if you observe that your cat eats more food than usual, but is still losing weight, it could be hyperthyroidism. A benign hormone-producing tumor in the thyroid gland that increases thyroid hormone levels will cause hyperthyroidism. Cats over the age of 10 are more prone to developing hyperthyroidism.  Also, older cats are more likely to get cancer than you think.  Studies have shown that about 30% of older cats die from cancer.  It is a common cause for cats with cancer to become underweight. If you can\'t find the cause of your cat\'s weight loss by observation alone, you should consider that your cat may be ill.  Cats, unlike dogs, tend to tolerate and hide their pain. If you suspect your cat has a disease, you must visit your veterinarian.</string>
    <string name="tv2_diag_text">" If your cat likes to eat and she's losing weight, then if you have multiple cats in the house, you should make sure that other cats are guarding the food and that they aren't eating. Also, since cats are very sensitive animals, the smell, taste, texture of food, type of food, moisture content of food, temperature of food, brand of food, location of food bowls, or how close a toilet or water bowl is nearby, etc. Cats don't eat well for a variety of reasons. However, if you are underweight rather than just skinny, you should keep in mind the possibility of disease. It is necessary to check whether it is not possible to eat properly due to complex oral diseases such as tooth resorption lesions, stomatitis, tooth decay, bleeding in the mouth, pain, wounds, and fractures. Unexplained weight loss can be a sign of illness. If you suspect a cat's disease, you must visit a veterinarian."</string>
    <string name="tv3_diag_text">The two main causes of skinny cats are not eating enough food or consuming more calories than they consume. Cats who are under psychological pressure such as anxiety and stress may lose weight because they do not eat well.  Cats are sensitive animals, so they are sensitive to every little thing, from other cats, moving house, strangers visits, excessive noise, strange smells, mirrors, food and water bowls, toilet location, a messy house, to a changed time to come to your house. It can be stressful. Cats love to go through their day on a regular schedule, and any change comes with stress. Or, if you have a cat that is too active, try to control her weight by changing the food or increasing the amount of food to suit her taste.</string>
    <string name="tv4_diag_text">Your cat is currently at a healthy weight. Keep your happy cat on regular exercise and good eating habits to keep her weight as stable as it is now.</string>
    <string name="tv5_diag_text">Your cat is currently at a healthy weight. Keep your happy cat on regular exercise and good eating habits to keep her weight as stable as it is now.</string>
    <string name="tv6_diag_text">Your cat is a little chubby.  If your cat continues to gain weight, it is important to manage it from now on as it can become overweight and cause diseases such as arthritis, heart disease, and diabetes. Cats are difficult to take a walk outdoors, so it is recommended to play with toys indoors and exercise using the cat tower.  Cutting back on snacks is also a good idea.</string>
    <string name="tv7_diag_text">Your cat is currently overweight.  The basis of health management is how to control the amount of feed. If your cat has been neutered, it will gain weight easily, so changing the food to a diet food to control weight can help with weight management. Consuming a high-protein, low-carbohydrate, low-fat diet will allow you to keep your cat in shape without compromising her health.  As in humans, obesity can cause various diseases, so it is necessary to control the weight. Cats prefer limited meals rather than self-service meals, and it is not good to eat as much feed as she wants whenever she wants. If you\'re a cat is not active enough, it\'s a good idea to spend enough time playing with her. Use the cat tower, cat wheel, and various toys to make sure she doesn\'t get bored.</string>
    <string name="tv8_diag_text">Your cat is currently obese. If you\'re feeding her a lot of snacks in addition to her current feed, you should cut down on her snacks as well. Snacks, even in small portions, are high in calories. If it is difficult to stop snacking, it is recommended to reduce it gradually.  Obesity in cats shortens their lifespan and increases their chances of getting sick. You may think that there is no problem because you see her every day, but compared to ideal weight cats, overweight or obese cats have a 2.8 fold increase in mortality rate at the age of 8~12. However, excessively restricting food intake to lose weight rapidly can lead to fatty liver. Fatty liver is a common disease for street cats and abandoned cats, so it is recommended not to starve and go on a diet, consult a veterinarian as soon as possible, and test cats to control their diet and run appropriate weight loss programs.</string>
    <string name="tv9_diag_text">"Your cat is currently very seriously obese. Being overweight in cats can lead to reduced play time and depression. Even compared to a healthy-weight cat, your cat's life expectancy can be significantly shortened as well. If a cat is obese, the joints of the legs cannot support the weight, which can lead to degenerative arthritis, diabetes, pancreatitis, and respiratory diseases. When an energy imbalance occurs, the likelihood of developing serious diseases such as hypothyroidism, hyperadrenocorticism, and diabetes increases.  Managing an obese cat's diet can be difficult, especially in households with more than one cat. This is because some cats can eat food left behind by other cats. Another cat may overeat because of the stress of living with other cats. Feeding in another room may be helpful. If she doesn't eat right to lose weight rapidly, she can develop fatty liver. Severely overweight cats can take up to a year to reach their ideal physique.  It's hard to notice the changes in my cat every day, so it's a good idea to measure your weight or body fat percentage on a regular basis. In particular, severely obese cats are advised to first consult with a veterinarian who can help from a health checkup to the cause of obesity and diet control rather than excessive exercise or excessive diet control. After checking your cat's health with a veterinarian, you can succeed in managing your cat's health with proper nutrition and exercise rather than excessive diet control. "</string>
    <string name="warning">Warning</string>
    <string name="body_measure_text">Measure body circumference</string>
    <string name="leg_measure_text">Measure leg length</string>
    <string name="fillBlank">Please fill in the blank.</string>
    <string name="resultIs">Result is</string>
</resources>